This week's big up goes to me. You know why? Because it's been raining for days and I have
handled it. Okay. There's been leaks. There's been floods. There's been all types of things
that have to happen because when you own a house, the house be doing what the house do.
I want to give myself a big up for not calling my ex and cursing him out for leaving me in this
house to handle this by myself. Because a real one would have at the very least hit me and been
like, I know we don't rock with each other no more, but I know how that house do when it starts
to get raining like this. Today's letdown goes to using WWJD to justify getting a BBL. Influencer
and YouTuber Sophieology revealed that since getting her BBL procedure, she has developed
an abdominal infection. Now, let me be clear. We are not making light of her infection and we
sincerely hope that she gets better. However, she initially went viral and was quickly chastised
for saying that she had got spiritual permission from God to get the daggone BBL. What does
that even sound like? What, you know, what is that prayer? Like, dear God, show me a sign
that I need to expand my waistline. Y'all stay bringing God into things that he has no business
in. Okay. Leave God and Jesus, Allah, throw Dumbledore in there, leave all of them out of it.
You want to have a bigger booty, just go and get your bigger booty and pray that you don't
get an infection.
We are, we are, we are.